本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： iamazed Thesouthface 许块块 野兽派小忧桑 一一 小白 Yeah
校对： 用一条姨妈巾的阿休休和打狗棒   后期： 阿休休
在高中
In high school,
很多事情只要你愿意
there's practically no limit to the number of things
便当真可以不要底线 出人意料的是
you can try your hand at. In a surprise move,
最近我决定喜欢一下瑞安・夏依
I had recently signed up for liking Ryan Shay.
要是一年前的我看那边会想
A year ago, I would've looked over there and thought,
"一群四肢发达的蠢货"
"what a bunch of dumb jocks."
而现在我看见那边却想的是...
And now I look over there and think...
"嗨 瑞安"
"Hey, Ryan."
我想这次的领养风波
I think this whole adoption thing
给他通了一些人性
has really helped humanize him,
温蒂汉堡连锁店的总裁 改良了甜点口味
就好像我们对大卫・托马斯的感觉一样
you know, like when we found out about Dave Thomas.
突然间他做的冰冻甜点还是有那么一点儿甜的
Suddenly his frozen dairy dessert tasted bittersweet.
你好 奥塔曼小姐
Good day, Miss Altman.
继续保密 是吗?
Keeping it tight, I presume?
你什么毛病?
What's wrong with you?
我不太确定该不该
I didn't know if people at school
让学校的人知道我们的事
were supposed to know about us or not.
知道什么?
Know what?
当然是我俩那痴缠的爱
About our love and how tender it is.
别矫情了 我不介意
Don't be weird. I don't care.
你听到了吗 卡斯温?
You hear that, Chatswin?
她不介意!
She doesn't care!
我和特萨毫不怯于
Tessa and I aren't embarrassed
向世人展现我们缠绵的爱
to express how tender our love is.
非常非常痴缠!
It's extremely tender!
耶!
Yeah!
祝贺你 特萨
Congratulations, Tessa.
我没想到
I had no idea things
你俩能发展到痴缠的地步
were so tender between the two of you.
大家做梦都想不到
No one in their wildest dreams
你居然把到了橄榄球运动员
expected you to snag a football player.
这好比一个少了腿的运动员赢下了
It would be like that runner with no legs
奥运会跑步比赛
winning the Olympics.
谢谢
Thanks.
听着 你现在是橄榄球队的家属了
Listen, you're a football girlfriend now.
我们就不计你过去的种种消极和扭捏
And we're going to look past your negativity and smugness
张开怀抱欢迎你
and embrace you,
因为这是橄榄球队家属们应该做的
because that's what football girlfriends do.
在你熟知你的责任前可以先跟着我学
You can shadow me till you get the hang of it.
别担心 你有一个好老师
Don't worry. You're in good hands.
安布尔已经培养出了
Amber's trained some
许多非常优秀的橄榄球家属
of the best football girlfriends in the field.
你可以把这条写进你的大学申请里
You should put that on your college application.
我干吗要上大学?
Why would I go to college?
我已经觅到了我未来的夫君
I've already met my future husband.
从今往后 我要记得在做新的决定之前
From now on, before signing up for things,
一定先瞅一眼那些附加条款
I should remember to read the fine print.
看看这打印效果 看看这分辨率 乔治
Look at that fine print and look at the D.P.I., George.
看一下嘛!
Just look at it!
这台打印机是我这辈子见过的最好的东西
This printer is the best thing that's ever happened to me,
美国喜剧演员兼编剧
我还见过盖瑞・山德林
and I met garry Shandling.
有了这台打印机 我便能帮大家印证梦想
With this printer, I can finally print people's dreams come true.
不过这不是我的梦想 对不?
But this isn't my dream, right?
别傻了 你可是国王
Don't be silly. You're a monarch.
看看你这华丽又饱满的面庞 乔治?
See how lush and saturated you look, George?
连养乐多都说你的脸很饱满
Even Yakult said you look saturated.
好吧 谢谢你 达拉斯 你真贴心
Yes. Okay. Thank you, Dallas, this is very sweet.
我感动死了
I appreciate it.
我们是不是该做一些标签?
Should we start cutting the tabs?
我要去见诺亚
I have to go meet Noah.
- 乔治? - 哈?
- George? - Huh?
那是啥?
What is that?
哦 就是一些文件啥的
Oh. That's just some files and stuff.
它们哪里像文件
They don't look like files.
明明是我的海报
They look like more of my flyers.
对 我...我...不就这么说的
Yeah, that... that... that's what I said.
文...海报
File-ers.
我在查尔斯顿学习过一阵子
Sometimes my Southern accent comes out
所以说话有点南方口音
from my semester in Charleston.
- 亲亲宝贝 - 哦
- Honey child. - Oh.
我也想尽量对橄榄球家属们不要有偏见
I wanted to have an open mind about the football girlfriends.
但她们把这个变得异常困难
They just made it so damn hard.
这里就是我们
This is where we bake
准备点心袋的地方
the treats for the goody bags
到比赛日我们会把它送给我们的男友
that we give to our boyfriends on game day.
我们这样做不是为了一句感谢
We don't do it for the thank-yous
因为他们也不会说感谢
because they don't say thank you.
我们乐在其中
We do it because it's tons of fun.
这里就是我们帮男朋友们写作业的地方
So this is where we do our boyfriends' homework
这样他们才能专心练习
so they can focus on practice.
我们这样做是为了一句感谢吗?
So we do this for the thank-yous?
不 特萨 我们从不言谢
Tessa, no. There are no thank-yous.
我们这么做是为了让我们的男人专注于取胜
We do this because it helps our guys to concentrate on victory,
久而久之 你会感觉他们的胜利
and over time, their victories will start
就是自己的胜利
to feel like your victories.
这也是一种自我奖赏 你会明白的
And that's it's own reward. You'll see.
这是赛前动员会总部
And this is the pep rally nerve center.
哇
Wow.
简直就像...
Looks like...
血汗工厂
a sweatshop.
我们称之为奉献坑
We call it the devotion pit.
我们在这儿做汗衫 横幅
It's where we make the T-shirts, banners,
各种小道具来表达我们的爱意
and miscellaneous sundries that express our love,
忠贞和拥戴
loyalty, and allegiance.
由此看来你们基本上就像在扮演旧时代
So you girls are basically mindless servants
毫无主见任凭使唤的女仆
struggling to uphold outdated gender roles?
你总算明白了
Now you got it.
并且你祀奉时间越长
And the longer you serve,
你加油的声音就越响亮 你会明白的
the louder you cheer. You'll see.
是德里克
It's Derek.
加油 德里克! 正想给你打电话呢 宝贝!
Let's go, Derek! Way to dial that phone, baby!
回答得很好 琼
Good phone answer, Joan.
谢谢
Thanks.
杀了我吧
No.
德里克也许喜欢这样
Derek may have been into it,
但有些人会觉得这种忘乎所以的加油鼓劲
but some people find relentless cheer-leading...
让人窒息 你知道 对我来说
Stifling. You know, to... to me,
每一张海报也好像在说
each one of those flyers might as well say,
"我蔑视你 乔治・奥塔曼
"I judge you, George Altman.
我蔑视你因为你不够成功"
I judge you for not being successful enough."
达拉斯本来就很挑剔
Dallas is judge-y. She is.
我们刚认识的时候 我还不是天窗之王
When she met me, I was not a skylight king.
听着 如果你是天窗之王
Look, if you're the skylight king,
那她就是皇后
then she's the queen.
行了 伙计们 那正是他们所追求的
All right, and that, my friends, is what they all want.
他们要地位 他们要安定
They want status. They... they want stability.
的确如此
They do.
要不然我干嘛当牙医
Why do you think I became a dentist?
哥路子可宽着呢
I could've been anything.
你看过我在高低杠上无所不能的样子么?
Have you ever seen me on the uneven bars?
他就像只老鹰 带手臂的
He's like an eagle with arms.
还带腿
And two legs.
还带张猴子脸 他长得挺像猴子
And a monkey's face. He's like a monkey.
他们凭什么把这些角色强加于我们 不公平
It doesn't seem fair that they can thrust these roles upon us.
迫使我们将自己的小世界建于地下室
Forcing us to build miniature cities in our basements.
我正在这么做
I'm building a miniature city in my basement.
- 挺不错的 - 好吧
- It's actually pretty cool. - Okay.
忘了什么天窗
Forget skylights.
如果现在给你机会干一番事业 你想做什么?
If you could start any business right now, what would it be?
那必须得是玩音乐的
I'd be in the business of rocking.
坏男孩
Ooh! Bad boy.
几年前我加入过一个老爸乐队
I was in a dad band a few years ago.
我负责贝斯
I played the bass guitar.
有个小妞很热情 我叫她罗达
Slapped her silly. Named her Rhoda.
罗达:美剧"罗达"里女主的名字
我超爱那部电视剧
I'm a big fan of that TV show.
爱死了 一集不落
Loved it. Never missed an episode.
伙计们 我们是当爸的 会摇滚的老爸
Guys, we're dads... dads who rock.
我们现在干嘛
Why is it
为毛不重振摇滚雄风?
we are not rocking out together?
- 是啊 干嘛不 - 问得好!
- I don't know. - That's a good question!
接下来怎么办?
Then what say ye?
老爸们 我们是不是该重拾自我
Dads, shall we redefine who we are
成为我们想成为的人?
and define who it is we want to be?
对 我们是不是得实实在在干一场
Yea, verily, shall we do something
真正逍遥法外一次?
that our partners can't control or dictate?
我们是不是把乐队取名叫"希拉的男宠"?
Shall we call our band "Sheila's Pets"?
不 弗雷德 这不行
No, Fred. No, we shall not.
这名字太糟了
That is a terrible name.
噢
Oh.
你跟那些橄榄球姑娘们处得怎样?
So how are you and the football girls getting along?
好极了
Great.
我就知道你们会合得来
I knew you'd hit it off.
安布尔有一段很有趣的经历
Amber's had a really interesting journey.
她以前老想跟我们侧边锋罗纳多约会
She always wanted to date Renaldo, our tight end,
但她那时候是个胖妞
but she used to be fat.
后来她减肥成功...
Then she lost a ton of weight...
他们就好上了
and then they hooked up.
不会吧 真的诶 真的很有趣
No. Yeah, that's really interesting.
可不是 太有趣了 不仅有趣还很励志
Yeah, it is interesting. It's interesting and it's inspiring.
太励志了
Really inspiring.
她的故事真的很棒
Yeah, she's got a great story.
正好提醒了我 我说好了12:45
Oh. Ah, that reminds me, I'm supposed to give Renaldo
跟罗纳多碰头
a noogie at 12:45.
我得先走了 糟糕
I better go. Shoot.
拜
Bye.
拜拜 拜
Bye-bye. Bye.
等下 你刚真觉得那姑娘的故事
So wait. Did you actually think that girl's story
- 有意思? - 不
- was interesting? - Nope.
对嘛 那你为啥不跟瑞安实话实说?
Right. So why aren't you being honest with Ryan?
你知道有时我会
Okay, you know how sometimes I can...
泼冷水 或者说自鸣得意?
be a little negative or... smug?
- 超爱说教 - 没错
- Preachy at times. - Right.
- 噼里啪啦没完 - 行了 丽莎 是
- Soapbox-y. - Okay, Lisa. Yep.
我在尽力改
I'm... I'm trying not to do that.
我想给他多点支持
I'm just trying to be supportive.
有意思
Interesting.
我看要跟大块头橄榄球健将约会
Well, I guess conformity's a small price to pay
这点服从的小代价还是值的
if you want to date a big, beefy football player.
现在是怎样 橄榄球比曲棍球高级吗
So what, football's a better sport than lacrosse?
是的 马利克
Yes, Malik.
别理他
Ignore him.
也许跟瑞安约会就注定了这一切 不是吗
Maybe this is what it means to be dating Ryan, right?
你看 有些人的体质
You know, some people's physiques
更适合去打曲棍球
lend themselves more to lacrosse,
曲棍球可比看上去难多了
which... which is a lot harder than it looks.
你这是给自己难堪呢 马利克
You are embarrassing yourself, Malik.
不 你才丢脸 在橄榄球队员面前摇尾乞怜?
No, you are. Fawning over football players?
我倒想看看他们用曲棍球护球时
I'd like to see one of them make a fast break
如何来个快攻
while maintaining his cradle.
没人懂你在说什么 马利克
Nobody knows what you're talking about, Malik.
想坐那边...
Do you want to go sit...
不不 吃你的 别引围观
No. No. Eat your food. Don't cause a scene.
好嘞 今晚我们要做
Okay, so tonight we're working
巨型横幅
on the giant paper banner
动员大会上全队会穿过横幅
that the team will run through at the pep rally.
沿袭惯例 我们用泡泡笔和闪光笔
Typically, we work with puffy pens and glitter,
不过你要是想试试新花样
but if you want to try something else...
免了吧 还是用
Don't. It's best if you just stick
泡泡笔和闪光笔
with the puffy pens and glitter.
好吧
Okay.
就爱你的激情 特萨
I love your enthusiasm, Tessa.
好了 搞得定不?
All right. You got this?
我在乐队里可是举足轻重的
I've played my fair share of "rock band."
我说的是演奏"光子黑洞"的那四人
I'm talking four stars for "Black Hole Sun"
太 "专业"了 哥们
on "Expert," brosef.
好嘞 还不错嘛
All right, not bad.
有点疯克的赶脚
Getting funky now.
疯克 我今晚要疯克罗达全家
Funky? I'm gonna funking funk the funk out of Rhoda tonight.
罗达那个贱人
Rhoda's a filthy lady.
这真的太棒了 兄弟们 太棒了
This is pretty sweet, guys. Pretty sweet.
我得说 骗希拉我有业务
I have to say, it felt good to finally tell Sheila
得赶紧去的感觉真好
I found a deer tick and had to run to urgent care.
好嘞 我在此宣布老爹的逆袭
Okay, I... I hereby declare the first rehearsal
或者说老爹的大破坏
of full-on Fatherly Assault
第一次彩排
or Fathers of Mass Destrucktion
开始了!
in session!
哟!
Yo!
明白了 所以希拉的男宠都没资格参选
I see. So Sheila's Pets isn't even on the ballot.
是的 而且... 既然我们谈到这问题
No, and... and since we're talking about it,
我还把"中国小鸡"从演奏列表中去掉了
I'm also vetoing the "Chickity China" song from the set list.
- 什么?! - 是的 那不是歌曲名
- What?! - Yeah, that's not the name of the song,
而且没人想唱
and no one wants to sing it.
没人想唱中国小鸡吗?
Nobody wants to sing about Chinese chicken?
- 我不... - 没... 我们都不想
- I don't. - N... neither of us do.
# 中国小鸡啊 中国的小鸡 #
Chickity China, the Chinese chicken
是的 我对这歌很熟 但还是不行
Yes, I'm familiar with it. Still a no.
坐下 排练吧 开始咯
Sit down. Let's do this. Here we go.
- 那是青蛙吗? - 什么?
- Is that a frog? - What?
你...在横幅上画青蛙吗?
Are you... are you drawing a frog on the banner?
你不...你不该这么做
You're not... you're not supposed to.
噢 我...
Oh. I...
只是...
just...
我知道怎么画 所以...
know how to draw them, so...
是啊 我还是会...会乖乖写字
Yeah. I would... I would just stick to the letters,
因为如果我们画画
because if we draw pictures,
运动员们就会停下来看 而不是...
the players will stop and look at 'em instead of...
毁掉我们花一整晚弄的杰作吗?
Destroying the artwork we spent all night making?
你看起来有点烦躁
You seem a little bit on edge.
试试剪掉这个尖头 会让你有点晕
If you snip the tip, you can catch a buzz.
这样时间会过得比较快
Makes the night go faster.
是嘛 我知道另一种方式来消磨时间
Yeah. I know another way to make the night go by faster.
知道是什么吗? 回家!
Know what it's called? Going home!
特萨
Tessa.
你小声点
Keep your voice down.
你说啥? 噢 你觉得
What's that? Oh, you think
我们不能画青蛙很无语? 我也觉得!
it's dumb we can't draw frogs? I agree!
我... 我没有...我没那样说过
I... I never... I... I never said that.
拜托! 我肯定大家有很多想做的事情
Come on! I'm sure there's all sorts of things you girls
但你们不能做 因为都耗在这儿了
wish you could do, but you can't, because you're here.
你们知道比耗这儿更好的是什么吗?
You know what's better than being here?
没有更好了 她喝醉了
There's nothing better. She's drunk.
我闻到她身上有酒味
I smell alcohol on her breath.
好吧 那就是...
Well, it's called...
回家
Going home.
我本不想搞什么临时演讲 但我忍不住了
I didn't want to get on a soapbox, but I am on one.
姑娘们 你们的需求和运动员们一样重要
Girls, your needs are just as important as a football player's.
像这边的斯蒂芬妮 她饿了
Look at Stephanie here. She's hungry.
她想出去吃点东西
She wants to go out for a slice.
她怎么知道的?
How did she know that?
还有你
And you.
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?
我是德里克的女朋友
I'm Derek's girlfriend.
我是问你的名字 孩儿?
What is your name, child?
我...想说...叫琼
I... want to say... Joan.
我猜你就是
I bet you do.
你看起来就叫琼
You look like a Joan.
还有看看那个用沾满血的运动衫
And what about that girl over there
包着手的女孩
with the bloody Jersey wrapped around her hand?
她不用去看下医生吗?
Shouldn't she be seen by a doctor?
肖恩说在我脑子里
Sean says it's in my head.
不在你脑子里
It's not in your head.
你的手在流血
You are bleeding from your hand.
她需要紧急护理
She should be in urgent care,
而我们应该呆在家里看电视
and we should all be at home watching TV.
郊区故事美国播放时间
现在是周三晚上九点半
It is 9:30 on a Wednesday night,
一定在演些精彩的节目
and there has gotta be something good on.
我要回家去看了
I'm going home to watch it.
谁和我一起?
Who's with me?
# 日复一日我愈发惆怅 #
Day after day I'm more confused
# 我望着倾盆大雨中的闪电发呆 #
and I look for the light through the pouring rain
# 你知道这是一场无法退却的游戏 #
you know that's a game that I hate to lose
# 况且我还有些紧张 #
and I'm feeling the strain
# 是不是有些丢脸 哦 #
yeah, ain't it a shame? Oh
# 来首歌吧 小伙子们 好让心情释放 #
give me the beat, boys, and free my soul
# 我多想沉迷于你的摇滚 #
I want to get lost in your rock 'n' roll
# 随节奏逍遥飘散 #
and drift away
# 哦 #
oh
# 来首歌吧 小伙子们 好让心情释放 #
give me the beat, boys, and free my soul
# 多想沉迷于你的摇滚 #
I want to get lost in Fred's rock 'n' roll
# 就在今天 #
today
# 哦 随节奏逍遥飘散 # 弗雷德!
Oh! Drift away, Freddie!
# 随节奏逍遥飘散 #
Drift away!
# 耶 #
Yeah!
你们几个到底在做什么哟?
What in blue blazes are you doing?
- 希拉...- 你们难听的噪音
- Uh, Sheila... - Your filthy noise is
污染了整个邻里
polluting the entire neighborhood,
尤其是领唱的
particularly the lead vocals.
你唱歌跑调 乔治 跑调太厉害
You're pitchy, George, very pitchy.
但是贝斯手还不错 对不?
But the base was good, right?
- 我跑调? - 没错
- I'm pitchy? - Yeah.
好啊 我倒想看看你能强哪去
Okay. I'd like to see you do better.
好啊
Okay.
"梭鱼" 开始
"Barracuda." Hit it.
# 所以这不是结束 #
So this ain't the end
# 我再一次见到你 #
I saw you again
# 就在今天 #
today
# 不得不带着我的心离开 #
I had to turn my heart away
# 像太阳般的微笑 #
smiled like the sun
# 送给每个人 #
kisses for everyone
# 吻和传奇 永不落幕 #
and tales, it never fails
# 你躺在低低的杂草中 #
you lying so low in the weeds
# 我打赌你会伏击我 #
I bet you gonna ambush me
# 你会为我而倾倒 #
you'd have me down, down, down
# 难道不是吗 梭鱼? #
now wouldn't you, barracuda?
# 噢噢噢噢 #
Oh, oh, oh, oh
这样...
So...
叫希拉的男宠么?
Sheila's Pets?
不 伙计
No, man.
这... 这可是老爸乐队
Th... this is a dad band.
不过希拉 不可否认真的很棒 有目共睹
But Sheila is undeniable. You saw her.
兄弟们...
Guys...
我这一辈子加入过的乐队多了去了...
I have been in a lot of bands in my life...
中学朋克乐队 大学高音乐队
high school punk bands, college alt bands,
在挣脱合唱团壮大前
I was briefly a member of Five for Fighting
我曾加入过... 而我这辈子从未
before they got big... and I have never in my life,
感到像今晚这样的 火花
felt the kind of spark... I did tonight.
你什么意思?
What are you saying?
我是觉得我们应该让希拉加入乐队
I'm saying I think we should let Sheila in the band.
噢 快清醒吧 哥们!
Oh. Get a hold of yourself, man!
兄弟们 我们有机会做的很好
Guys, we could be good!
你们明白那意味着什么吗?
Do you understand what that means?
我们可以成为最好的
We could be good,
不是什么老爸乐队 而是真正的乐队
not dad-band good, but real-band good.
瞧 我之所以加入老爹的大破坏
Look, I joined Fathers of Mass Destroction...
或者可以叫父亲乐队
or I was also thinking Meinvater Band...
是因为...
because...
我们不光为了自己玩了
we stood for something.
我们代表着广大男同胞不必和老婆们在一起
We stood for not hanging out with our wives
能有权自由支配晚上的时间
and taking back the night.
我们说好的一起玩呢 乔治?
What about the hanging out, George?
我们说好的薯条和蘸酱呢?
What about the chips and dip?
兄弟们 抱歉
Guys, I'm sorry.
我想 考虑到我是主唱
I think considering I'm the lead singer
兼吉他手 兼乐队创始人
and the guitarist, and I started this band,
这件事上你们得听我的
I gotta make the call on this one.
我必须为希拉的男宠着想
I have to do what's best for Sheila's pets.
很好...
Well...
那你就孤军奋战吧
then you do it alone.
朋友
My friend,
一个人哦
you do it alone.
我们走 弗雷德
Come on, Fred.
车库还不是唯一士气尽散的地方
Our garage wasn't the only place spirits were down.
最后
And finally,
人家永远愿意花一块钱买票看的四分卫
the quarterback that I would pay a dollar for...
只会看他一个哦
the one, the only,
瑞安 "我们的雄霸" 夏依
Ryan "The Body" Shay!
来吧 卡斯温
Come on, Chatswin.
士气在哪里?
Where's your spirit?!
你妹啊?
What the hell?
我们的橄榄球家属呢?!
Where's all the football girlfriends?!
这个队伍完全没有活力了
There is very little pep at this rally.
这事儿恐怕是因我的临时演讲而起
I might've had one of my soapbox incidents.
好吧 我貌似把她们从劳役中解放了
Yeah, I kinda liberated the girls from their servitude
而且不合时宜的激励了她们一下
and unintentionally empowered them.
瑞安会弄死你哦
Mm. Ryan's gonna kill you.
这事谁他妈干的?!
Who did this?!
呵啊?!
Huh?!
有种站出来
Show yourself!
没关系 打起精神 兄弟们!
It's okay. Get up, boys!
没他们我们也会赢!
We can win still!
会赢
We can win.
正当我浇灭瑞安胜利的梦想时
While I had dashed Ryan's dreams of glory,
- 乔治花钱请了一帮乐手...- 耶!
- George had hired some session musicians... - Yeah!
开始实现他的梦想... 和希拉一起
And was making his own dreams come true... with Sheila.
# 我要吃糖 #
I want candy
# 嘿 我要吃糖 #
hey, I want candy
# 呼! #
Hoo!
来点激情 乔治 赶紧的
Put some stank on it, George. Come on!
呼! 呼!
Whoo! Whoo!
好的 休息五分钟 休息五分钟
All right, let's take five. Let's take five.
表现很棒 伙计们
Sounds great, guys.
我琢磨唱摇滚会渴! 所以
I know rocking's a thirsty business, so I...
哦! 哦 希拉
Oh! Oh, Sheila.
俺们不接受请求
We don't take requests.
不是 我只是以为乔治的乐队里只有老爸们
No. I just thought George's band was a daddy-only thing.
你不是这么告诉我的嘛 老爹?
Isn't that what you told me, daddy?
这个嘛 本来是这样的 但是后来...
Well, you know what? It was, uh, but then...
- 关键是 额...- 乔治?
- The thing is, uh... - George?
- 咋啦? - 告诉你家小可爱够了
- Yeah? - Tell your piece to hit it.
不好意思 我们这不要小撒娇
Sorry. We have a no-Yoko policy.
好了
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
我们输了
We lost the game.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们开场没有从纸糊的横幅中穿过去
No one even got to run through a paper banner made of paper.
我知道
I know.
那是橄榄球比赛中大家最喜欢的环节 特萨
That's everyone's favorite part of football, Tessa.
一半人是因为这个才开始玩橄榄球的
That's why half of us started playing in the first place.
我们如何击败一只从横幅中冲出来的队伍
I mean, how can we beat a team that got to run through paper
而我们没有机会
when we haven't had the advantage
穿越纸糊的横幅?
of running through paper ourselves?
是不是你们有点太在意
Is it possible you're putting too much importance
冲出纸糊的横幅了?
on running through paper?
是不是你脑子被驴踢了?
Is it possible that you're crazy?
你看 瑞安 那些给你们做横幅的妹子...
Look, Ryan, those girls making your banners...
她们也应该去追逐自我啊
they're out there pursuing their own interests.
她们可以吃披萨
They're eating pizza
融入大家的圈子中
and becoming well-rounded people.
她们生活的目标
Their sole purpose in life
不可能只是崇拜他们的男朋友
cannot be to worship their boyfriends.
是你干的?
You did this?
我其实没打算拆散组织 好吧 是我做的
I didn't mean to dismantle the system, but yeah, I did.
很抱歉如果让你不开心了
And I'm really sorry if you're upset.
我早该知道你根本不想
I should've known you didn't really want
融入我的圈子
to fit in with my friends.
你永远都想打破成规
You always have to shake it up.
你永远要煽动
You always have to make
别人...思考
people... think.
我就是个思想家 瑞安 我总会思考
I am a thinker, Ryan. I think.
我以为那正是你喜欢我的原因
I thought you liked that about me.
再想想 思想家
Think again, thinker.
再想想
Think again.
达拉斯 让俺解释一下
Dallas, let me explain, please.
没啥可解释的
There's nothing to explain.
你跟你的小朋友们组小乐队
You started your little band with your little friends
你就可以逃避跟我一起做有趣的印刷工作
so you could avoid doing fun printing jobs with me.
我知道 达拉斯 现在我...
Look, Dallas, now I...
我知道你想要我变得有钱有势
I know you want me to be rich and powerful
事业蓬勃发展
and to grow my business into some huge empire,
但是内心深处我不想承认我是这样...
but part of me is unwilling to admit that I am this...
也 也不是这样
and... and not this.
一个马桶?
A toilet?
哦 这本应该是"滚石乐队"的
Oh, that was supposed to be "Rolling Stone."
你应该懂我的意思
But you know what I mean.
乔治 我会支持你的 无论你要成为
George, I will support you whether you want to be
天窗王或是乐队王
the skylight king or the King of Leon.
是谁都无所谓
Whoever the hell he is.
真的吗? 但是
Really? Because
你为了我这么辛苦做了这些传单
you were coming at me so hard with those flyers.
这... 这让我觉得...
It... it kind of felt like...
你想要改变我
Like you were trying to change me.
我花了七千块买复印机 乔治
I spent $7,000 on a printer, George.
七千块啊
$7,000.
我当然想要它有用武之地
I sure as hell better use it.
你看
Look,
当女人在她不需要的东西上
sometimes when a woman spends too much money
花了一大笔钱的时候
on something she really doesn't need,
她就想要让每个人认为
she tries to cram it down everyone else's throats
她花钱是值得的
to justify the purchase.
你肯定能理解的
Surely you can understand that.
我很抱歉 达拉斯
Well, I'm sorry, Dallas.
我... 我可能是有点自卫敏感
I... I guess I was being a little defensive
因为史蒂文...
because Steven was such...
在我的心灵留下了一道深刻的划痕?
An absolute skid mark on the pristine panties of my soul?
不管这个人多么有钱
No matter how much money that man had,
都不够留住我的心
it wasn't enough to keep me.
我很高兴听你这么说
I'm glad to hear you say that.
嘿 你猜怎么着?
Hey. You know what?
我们的乐队需要一些传单
Our band does need some flyers.
你认识的人谁有一台七千块的复印机吗?
Now do you know anyone that has a $7,000 printer who could help?
我正好有哦
You know I do.
好的
Okay.
你们乐队的名字叫什么?
What's the name of your band?
额...
Uh...
拦截
Interception.
有意思
Funny.
谢谢
Thanks.
我很抱歉...
I'm really sorry...
昨天的事情
about yesterday.
可能是我反应有点过度了
It's possible that I overreacted a little bit.
但是你让我思考了
But you made me think.
我过去不想思考
I didn't want to,
但是你改变了我 你总会让我思考
but you made me, like you always do,
然后我觉得...
and I think...
每个人都需要被鼓励
that everyone needs to be cheered for,
不只是我们这些队员
not just us guys.
所以... 兄弟们?
So... bros?
这是什么?
What's this?
我想要你感受穿过这张纸的感觉有多棒
I want you to see how good it feels to run through paper.
我不想冲破这张纸
I don't want to run through paper.
我为你思考了 现在你也要为了我试一下
I did your thing. Now you're gonna try mine.
我想要你知道有人为你加油的感觉
I want you to know how good it feels
是多么棒
to have someone rooting for you.
好的 来吧
Okay. Fine.
3 2 1!
Three, two, one!
冲啊！
Go!
我不得不承认 这感觉确实很爽
I had to admit, it was pretty exhilarating...
还有... 一点丢人
and... a little embarrassing.
喔！粉碎这些数字 特萨!
Whoo! Crush those numbers, Tessa!
搞定数学！
Destroy that math!
耶!
Yeah!
所有的公园都可以随意着装吗?
Are all the parks clothing-optional?
是的 不过虽然如此 我还没有找到任何
Yeah, but I haven't been able to find any nude figurines
有裸像的 所以...
at that scale, so...
决定了
Okay.
嗯
Hmm.
"中国小鸡"
"Chinese Chicken."
出自加拿大摇滚乐队
作为歌词意译为"消沉"
然后 你
And, you,
你给乐队起个名字 什么样的名字都行
you get to name the band whatever you want.
我不知道 乔治
I don't know, George.
我觉得这事差不多玩完了
I think it's kind of ruined now.
对 还有如果你这么喜欢希拉
Yeah. And if you love Sheila so much,
干嘛不跟她结婚?
why don't you marry her?
求你了 别
Please don't.
好吧 你们有权对我生气
Look, you have every right to be upset with me,
但是这是... 这可是...
but it's... it's been...
# 一周前你看着我 #
One week since you looked at me
# 你把头歪向一边 说"我很生气" #
cocked your head to the side and said "I'm angry"
# 五天前你嘲笑我 #
Five days since you laughed at me
# 我如此消沉失意 #
chickity China the Chinese chicken
不 弗雷德 不 错了 还没到这句
No, Fred. No. No, it's too soon.
绝对到了
It's never too soon.
# 当我打破韵律 热辣得像芥末酱 #
Hot like wasabi when I bust rhymes,
# 性感如同黎安・莱姆丝 #
big like leann rimes
# 因为我估摸着 #
because I'm all about value
# 贝特・肯普菲尔特要被揍 #
bert kaempfert's got the mad hits
# 你想要跟我斗智斗勇 #
you try to match wits
# 你想要控制我 但是我突出了重围 #
you try to hold me but I bust through
# 打算休息一下 打个马虎眼 #
gonna make a break and take a fake
# 我想要烂醉如泥地摇摆 #
I'd like a stinkin' achin' shake
# 我喜欢香草味 它是所有味道里 #
I like vanilla, it's the finest
# 最棒的 #
of the flavors.